在上一集中
Previously on Transformers Prime...
尽管下载到的铁堡数据不完整
The download of the Iacon database may have been incomplete
但我们已经拥有了战舰所破译的四个坐标
but we now possess four sets of coordinates decoded by the ship.
如果我们想赶在霸天虎之前得到铁堡的遗物
If we are to have any hope of recovering the Iacon relics before the Decepticons do
我们就必须分头行动
we must divide our resources.
派出多支小队 同时前往这四个地点
Dispatching multiple squadrons will enable us to pursue all four coordinates simultaneously.
保持警惕 隔板
Be on your guard, Bulkhead.
救护车 到这边来！
Ratchet, come here.
铁堡数据库
The Iacon database.
它下载到我们的主机上来了！
It's downloading into our mainframe.
哈哈哈！拉斐尔你真是个天才！
Hahahahaha! Rafael, you are a genius!
隔板回来了 福勒探员
Bulkhead's coming through, Agent Fowler.
我等不及要分享这个消息了！
I can't wait to share the news.
不…！
No!
谁是你们中的最强者？
Who is the fiercest among you?
说到凶残 什么也不及一整窝的机器昆虫
There is no greater ferocity than Insecticon hive
但您一定要从我们中间挑一个的话…
but if you would to choose one among us...
…我是硬壳
... I am Hardshell.
你去替我拿回一样东西 硬壳
You will retrieve something for me, Hardshell
并消灭一切敢于阻挠你的人！
and annihilate everything that gets in your way!
散开！迅速行动 踏上征途！
Divide and do not hesitate to conquer!
神子和杰克陪大黄蜂还有阿尔茜前往
Miko and Jack will accompany Arcee and Bumblebee.
太好了！
Yes!
开始传送
Initiate transport...
同时开始定位另外三组坐标
... and triangulate coordinates of the other three relics.
这可不是远足 神子
That was some trick, Miko.
那从威震天鼻子底下扫描情报呢？
You mean, swiping intel from right under Megatron's nose?
我是领袖卫队的一员！
Just doing my part for team Prime!
哦 我得走了 小隔
Oh, got to go Bulk!
等我回来再跟你讲整个故事
I'll tell you all about it when we get back.
等等我！
Wait up!
- 照顾好她 小蜂\N- 照顾好他 神子
- Take care of her, Bee.\N- Take care of him, Miko.
隔板 准备出发
Bulkhead, prepare for departure.
你将前往赤道
You are headed for the equator.
我去体会热带风情了 雷霆救援队来袭！
I'll prep for tropical weather... wrecker style.
拉斐尔和福勒探员负责联络和进行传送
Rafael and Agent Fowler will be your communications and transportation hub.
我吃不下芝士汉堡包了 呃！
I can't. That's cheeseburger!
联络 嗯？
Communications, huh?
保持警惕 隔板
Be on your guard, Bulkhead.
哦 哦！
Oh...
比霸天虎兵营还要难闻！
Smells worse than a Decepticon barraks.
真是个藏遗物的好地方！
Fine place to hide a relic.
基地 我找不到任何遗物的信号
Base, I can't find any sight of the relic.
你能确定坐标吗？
Can you reconfirm coordinates?
正在测定你的位置 隔板
Triangulating your position, Bulkhead.
你的位置没有错误
You're at the correct location.
哦 得来点咖啡
Oh... Need coffee...
那就是坐标错了 这里什么都没有…
And the coordinates are wrong, 'cause there is nothing here.
…不过有东西来了！
But something's coming.
威震天派只虫子来替他干见不得人的勾当
Leave it to Megatron to send a bug to do his dirty work.
你也不是什么清白的货色 救援队小子！
You know a thing or two of dirty work yourself, Wrecker.
我认识你吗？
Do I know you?
我认识你的同类
I know your kind...
因为我这辈子碾碎的救援队员已经数不清了
... as I have crossed more than a few Wreckers in my time.
瞧你这个大块头
Now you see the thing about bugs your size.
等我砸碎你时 得是多大的一块废铁！
They make a bigger mess when I smash them.
救护车 病毒编写完成
Ratchet, the virus is coded.
开始上传
Commencing upload.
拉夫 我猜到遗物的位置了
Raf, I have a bead on the relic.
拉夫正忙 我来接手
Raf is busy. I'll take it from here.
福勒！睡得怎么样？
Fowler? How was your beauty sleep?
很好 梦到你终于对我尊重点了
Fine. Jumped I finally got low respect from you.
继续做梦吧！
Keep dreaming.
你的情况？
What's your status?
在坐标处一无所获
Came up empty to provided coordinates.
但我猜想应该是早期的熔岩流把遗物带下了山
But I'm figuring old lava flow might have carried relic downhill.
熔岩不会烧毁遗物吗？
Wouldn't that just burn it up?
遗物能经受住星际旅行
This relic survived interstellar transport
我相信它们禁得住岩浆…
I'm sure that can stand multi....
…哦 该死！
... oh, scrap.
怎么了？
What is it?
我在漏能量 机器昆虫把我伤得不轻
I'm leaking Energon. Insecticon hit me hard.
机器昆虫？
Insecticon?
大概垫片没有受损
Probably not the gasket wheels.
没什么可担心的 相信我
Nothing to worry about.
他比我惨得多
Trust me, he's a way worse shape than I am.
他留了我一条命
The Wrecker left me alive.
这是致命的错误
The last mistake he will ever make.
找到你了！
There you are!
盖子打开了！
Got the lid off.
啊哦 基地 我们有麻烦了
O-oh. Base... we have a problem.
隔板 怎么了？
Bulkhead, what is it?
我找到遗物了 是一个能量储存块
I found the relic. It's a cash of Energon.
那很好 不是吗？
That's good, right?
不 不 不 不是这种好法
No-no-no, not this kind.
它被称为毒能
It's known as Tox-En.
接触后会产生恶心和头晕
Causes nausy and dizziness upon contact.
长期暴露其中会使我们麻痹
Prolong exposal weakens us to the point of paralysis.
最终 熄灭我们的火种
And then... it snuffs out our sparks.
那还说这么多干嘛？
Well, what do you talking to me for?
快远离那个毒能！
Get far away from that Tox-En. Prompto.
如果它真像传说的那般致命
If it is as deadly as you say...
虎子们也不会想得到它！
... the 'Cons won't want it either.
不 他们十分想得到它
No, they'll want it even more.
在塞博特恩的战争中
During the war for Cybertron.
威震天找到一种提炼天然毒能的方法
Megatron figured out a way to refine raw Tox-En...
制作成一种大规模杀伤性武器
... turning it to a weapon of mass destruction.
我目睹了一整支部队因中毒而全军覆没
I witnessed when entire unit wiped out by the sickness.
我绝不能把这东西留给虎子们用来为非作歹
No way I can leave this stuff for 'Cons to find and abuse.
那么把它带回来
So bring it back here.
拉夫？打开环陆桥
Raf? Open a Ground Bridge.
不行 就算我们能找到安全的容器保存它
Forget it. Even if we had a safe place to store it...
这东西的潜在威胁也很大 不能冒险再让其他人接触它
... the stuff's way too potently risky to exposing the rest of us...
啊 我等会儿再联系你
I'll call you back.
我要用雷霆救援队的方式来处理这个东西
I gonna need to take care of this... Wrecker style.
嗯 在那里！
There.
不 等等！
No! Wait!
啊 毒能！
Tox-En.
什么 你带着它走？
Wait, you're carying it?
那东西不是有毒吗？
I thought that stuff was toxic.
是有毒 但是我需要与虫子们拉开距离
It is. But I needed to put some distance between me and the bugs.
好吧 那要怎么做？
Well, what now?
只有一个办法可以处理掉这堆冒气的东西
I'm gonna get rid of this steaming pile the only way I can.
我要把它扔进火山
I'm gonna lob it into the volcano.
那些昆虫怎么办？
What about the insect problem?
知道吗 我对反侦查很有心得
This isn't my first time aluding an enemy patrol, you know.
威震天陛下 我们要找的物品
Lord Megatron, the object we seek...
是毒能
It is Tox-En.
那你到底拿到了多少？
Exactly how much is in your possession?
一无所获 我的主人 一个汽车人…
None, my lord. An Autobot...
你不是最强的机器昆虫吗？
Are you not the fiercest Insecticon?
等等 你在远离火山？
Wait, you're moving away from the volcano?
完全正确…
Exactly.
下边！
Below.
没错… 从救援队那小子的伤口流下来的
Yes.  The Wrecker leaks from his wounds.
找到他！
Find him!
你留下了误导的踪迹 哈？
You did the false trail, huh?
我曾在敌人后方与部队走散时
I once pulled that trick when I got separated...
也用过这招
... from my unit behind enemy lines.
你什么时候到过敌人后方？
When where you ever behind enemy lines?
我以前可不是机器人保姆
I wasn't always a bot-sitter.
下次你该说你妈妈晚上没有帮你掖被子了
Next you gonna tell me your mother doesn't tuck you in at night?
这可是基本训练
That's as basic training.
训练做什么？秀场小丑吗？
Training as what? A rodeo clown?
你浪费了太多时间去陪神子玩怪物卡车了
You was been way too muc time in monster truck rallies with Miko.
我曾是一个游骑兵队员
I was an army ranger.
我们干得不比任何人差
We could wreck with the best of them.
谁能想到我们如此相像
Who knew you and I are so much alike.
拉斐尔 福勒探员恢复知觉了吗？
Rafael! Has Agent Fowler regained consciousness?
等一下 隔板
Stand by, Bulkhead.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
我在这儿 擎天柱
I'm here, Prime.
你那边是什么情况？
What's the situation?
我需要进入一处考察站 就在我所在的位置
I require access to a research facility at my current coordinates.
让我联系一下
Let me make a call.
只有雷霆救援队员
The dirty job.
干得了这样的脏活
That only a Wrecker can do.
来吧！
C'mon!
这是紧急情况
This is an emergency!
我们的卫星侦测到高危程度的太阳活动
Our satellites have detected dangerous solar flare activity!
我需要那个基地里的所有人员立刻撤离！
I need that entire station evacuated immediately!
听到了吗？
Do you hear me?
离开那里 马上！
Get out of there, now!
基地已经清空了 擎天柱
Base is clear, Prime.
尽量不要破坏设备
Try not to wreck the joint.
十分感谢 福勒探员
My thanks, Agent Fowler.
隔板 你还撑得住吗？
Bulkhead, are you holding up?
神子有什么消息吗？
Any word... from Miko?
不用担心她
Don't worry about her.
你得专注你自己的任务
You need to focus on your own mission.
好吧 我得…休息…一小会儿
Right. I... I need to... rest... just for a minute.
我知道这很难
I know it's tough
但我希望你能坚持到底
but I need you to stay the course.
隔板 隔板 隔板？
Bulkhead. Bulkhead! Bulkhead!
隔板 回答我 你这个生锈的水桶
Bulkhead! Answer me, you, rust bucket!
我在呢 游骑兵
I'm here, ranger.
啊 你吓到我了 黑大个
You had me scared two tonnes.
我…我做不到
I... I can't do it.
我不想听到这种话
I do not want to hear that kind of talk.
尤其不想从你这里听到
Especially from the likes of you.
我们都知道 你经历过的艰难险阻
We both know you've made it through worse.
趴下！趴下！
Down! Down!
不会 不会比这更糟 连吸屑虫都…
Not worse than this. Not even scraplets.
听着 战士
Look, soldier
你跟我一样清楚 这是个任务
you know as well as I do there is a mission...
你清楚为什么要接手这个任务
... and the reason why you take the mission.
荣誉…使命…
Honor... duty...
家人！这才是原因
Family! Which is why you need  to do whatever it takes to finish this job...
并且平安地回家
... and come home safely.
神子 我的职责是保护你…
Miko, I am supposed to be protecting you.
隔板 我待在十吨重的钢筋铁骨里面
Bulkhead. I'm strapped tight inside ten tons of metal muscles.
万无一失
I am protected.
神子 来看看 新的战伤
Miko, check it out. New battle scars.
喔！
Wow!
神子？
Miko?
我吐在脚垫上了 抱歉
I heaved on your floor mats. Sorry.
我在成为战士之前 是个工人
Before I became a warrior, I was a labourer.
我能造东西 也能拆东西
I can build stuff, I can break stuff.
我想和你一样 小隔
I wanna be just like you, Bulk.
不 你必须立即住手
No, you need to stop, now!
不行 小隔 我必须救你出去！
I can't, Bulk. I have to get you out of here...
隔板 我知道你内心的某个地方会一直记得我
Bulkhead, I know somewhere inside you always remember me.
我只是想让你知道
And I just want you to know...
我永远也不会忘记你…
I'll never forget you.
嗯 你是对的 福勒
You're right, Fowler...
我必须坚持下去 为了其他的汽车人 为了神子！
I gotta dig deep... for the other bots... for Miko!
他的行动不合理
There is no logic to his movements.
这些踪迹是用来误导我们的！
His trail is meant to lead us astray.
要找到救援队那小子
To find the Wrecker...
我们不能被牵着走
... we must not follow...
要合理分析
... we must anticipate.
哦 快到了
Almost there.
好样的 战士
That's right, soldier.
扔了那块石头 然后快回家!
Dump that rock and come on home.
我是福勒 什么事 神子？
Fowler. Miko, what is it?
什么？
What in Sam hill?
我这里正在紧要关头呢 你却要我…
I'm in the middle of a crisis here and you want me to...
…让他接电话
Uh, put him on the line.
救援队小子！
Wrecker!
放下那块石头 让我们来帮你解脱吧
Put down the rock and allow us to put you out of your misery.
我得先拍死些苍蝇…
Gotta swat some flies.
警告你 这是会传染的！
Fair warning.... I'm contagious.
帮我拿一会儿！
Hold this.
沃格先生 我是美国政府的特工威廉福勒
Mr. Vogel this is special Agent William Fowler of the United States government.
你特此被任命为星际关系部的
You are hereby deputized as an honorable Agent for the departement of...
嗯…荣誉探员
... interstellar relations.
隔板 你还在吗？
Bulkhead, you still with me?
我这里危机四伏 你居然把我撂到一边了？
I'm in the scrap and you put me on hold?
我要告诉你
I want you to know...
神子安然无恙 任务完成
Miko safe, mission accomplished.
这才是我的好姑娘
That's my girl.
躺好了
Scurrydown
联系战舰准备密闭容器
contact the warship for a containment unit.
隔板 能听到吗？
Bulkhead, do you read me?
救护车 到这边来
Ratchet, come here.
隔板 请回话
Bulkhead, please respond!
铁堡数据库？
The Iacon database?
它下载到我们的主机上来了！
It's downloading into our mainframe.
回答我 战士！
Answer me, soldier!
哈哈哈 拉斐尔你真是个天才！
Hahahahaha! Rafael, you are a genius!
你们能安静一下吗？
Will you keep it down?
你的火种是我的了 救援队小子
Your spark is mine, Wrecker.
想尝尝这个吗 嗯？
You want a taste of this? Do you?
接好了！
Catch!
福勒 任务完成
Fowler, mission accomplished.
看来你得 把我抱回去了
But you may have to... tuck me in.
拉夫 打开环陆桥 快！
Raf, open the bridge! Now!
不！
No!